{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e4c1cfba6a7878438d1"},"product_asin":"B08SR372S7","QAs":[{"question":"Can we wash oily or grease clothes","answer":"Yes...","votes":"0","username":"ABHISHEK KUMAR","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty will be covered by bosh or amazon...?","answer":"Obviously Bosch.","votes":"0","username":"Ashwin Sonagaj","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hi , is it normal to have water droplets and white water spots inside and on the grey rubber area, when u receive this item brand new?","answer":"Yeah it is normal and nothing to worry about. During pre dispatch inspection sometimes few droplets or spot remain even after cleaning. Just clean it.","votes":"0","username":"prathamesh thakur","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Waj2416sin 2022 modal ?","answer":"It's 2021 model...","votes":"0","username":"ABHISHEK KUMAR","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it requires a stand?","answer":"Its optional but better to have a stand. Also try stand price in market n try to buy from market as almost 50% saving if you buy from installation guy. They can quote any rate with or without invoice.","votes":"0","username":"Varun A.","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which year of model is this?","answer":"I think it is 2018.","votes":"0","username":"Shyam G Hathiramani","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we get latest model?","answer":"Sure..","votes":"0","username":"ABHISHEK KUMAR","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine have any mode which is only used for Drying ?","answer":"Yes there is.","votes":"0","username":"Anil Tiwari","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Periodical service is required?","answer":"It almost require service everyday. Don't buy Bosch, they did not do the right enginnering. They have a problem in the way they aligned the inlet pipe and how much ever pressure is there, it will not be able to take water.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whether stabilizer required for this washing machine if the voltage range in between 206- 210 volt? Kindly suggest a good stabilizer for this machine?","answer":"Not required.","votes":"0","username":"Ravichandran","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Dose this washing machine have Rat mesh?. If yes is it fiber or stainless steel mesh?","answer":"It has stainless steel mesh","votes":"0","username":"Gyan","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it be delivered to 2nd Floor","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Gyan","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"3D wash or 2D wash?","answer":"3D","votes":"0","username":"Gyan","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"The product is listed as 5-star energy rating. For the same model number, the Bosch website says no energy star rating. What is true?","answer":"Depend on your choice","votes":"0","username":"Gyan","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Tap symbol while washing is ok to use?","answer":"Nop","votes":"0","username":"Gyan","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which model year this","answer":"2022","votes":"0","username":"Gyan","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Has it belt based motor??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Gyan","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e4d1cfba6a7878438da"},"product_asin":"B08JYPDFXV","QAs":[{"question":"I have a Bosch 7kg washing machine. Can I place this dryer on top of the washing machine.","answer":"yes you can","votes":"0","username":"A Customer","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it only cloth dryer? Or is it washer+ dryer?","answer":"It's only Dryer. If you have any requirements for Washer+Dryer contact us @9911468008","votes":"0","username":"WONDERSHOPEE","date":"2022-06-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it a plug and play appliance. What is inlet pipe for","answer":"Yes its plug and play. Pipe is to drain out water from the dryer","votes":"0","username":"Gagan","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its says inbuilt heater.. is it the same as heater pump condensor? How much electricity is used in every load?","answer":"Yes it has a heat pump.","votes":"0","username":"Rajdeep Anand","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be wall hanged or stacked on front load washing machine?","answer":"Don't think you can hang it on the wall... But it can be stacked for sure, on top of front loading washing machine using accessories from Bosch.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"is this seller (E Sales India) an authorized reseller of bosch and will bosch india honor warranty on dryer bought on Amazon?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Rakesh Malik","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will demo provided and how ?","answer":"Yes you can contact bosch for demo and installation","votes":"0","username":"Gagan","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do clothes come out 100% dry ?\r\ndoes it require exhaust for moisture or does it have a box to collect moisture, can i keep it in a enclosed room?","answer":"Yes they come out 100% dry.  The machine can be kept in a room. There is a pipe that needs to be attached to the machine so that the water can be drained out from the machine","votes":"0","username":"Gagan","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can this be placed directly on the  washing machine mountable","answer":"Yes but only bosch washing machine.","votes":"0","username":"Gagan","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will this dryer be installed by the company?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Gagan","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it require a water outlet drain","answer":"Yes,  ideally. Alternatively, as a stop gap arrangement, you can collect water through the pipe in a small tub and throw it later","votes":"0","username":"Gagan","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why is there an inlet pipe in the Dryer?","answer":"Its an outlet pipe","votes":"0","username":"A Customer","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation included with this product?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Gagan","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have IFB 6.5 kg washing machine can i fix it top of the washing machine?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"WONDERSHOPEE","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"It this 5 star rated electricity rating machine","answer":"doesnt comes star rating","votes":"0","username":"WONDERSHOPEE","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be placed over washing machine inverted/upside down ??","answer":"YES","votes":"0","username":"WONDERSHOPEE","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e4e1cfba6a7878438e5"},"product_asin":"B08SR624PS","QAs":[{"question":"How many watts of mechine","answer":"0.2 kWh with 30degC program and as high as 1.9kwh with 95degC program. It varies with the temperature settings. But overall consumption is less.","votes":"0","username":"BASABATTINI MUNIMANI","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"this model manufacturing year?","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"vinay","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it anti Wrinkle ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Mohit","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What iis the dimension, it says 59 x 59.8 x 84.8 Centimeters whereas in the image it's different ?","answer":"no almost same","votes":"0","username":"vinay","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is inverter touch","answer":"touch is bit hard","votes":"0","username":"vinay","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has in built heater","answer":"Yes inbuilt heater","votes":"0","username":"Vijay raghawan","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it direct drive or belt","answer":"Drive","votes":"0","username":"Naveen Kumar","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can we put water  in machine when water tap is unavailable ?","answer":"Compulsory tap needed","votes":"0","username":"Vijay raghawan","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is inverted touch control","answer":"Simply touch like mobile phone display","votes":"0","username":"Vijay raghawan","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has in built heater","answer":"Yes it has in buit heater","votes":"0","username":"sunilkumar","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e4e1cfba6a7878438eb"},"product_asin":"B08J3KFLBT","QAs":[{"question":"Whether hardwater compatible??","answer":"Yes, but you have to do complete cleaning every month","votes":"0","username":"Red'D, Vijayawada","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it soften hard water?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Red'D, Vijayawada","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing date,country of manufacture of the particular item? is the drum of ss or chromium plated? qty of water consumed in single wash?","answer":"Complete drum built by SS 304 grade and any washing machine major components from BOSCH only in front loading washing machines the best BOSCH.Made in India  only.Thanks & RegardsVenkataramana Reddy Kichilisee less","votes":"0","username":"Shashikanth Doll","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"which year manufacturing is this product","answer":"You will know before you place the order","votes":"0","username":"Red'D, Vijayawada","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it dry the clothes?","answer":"No, you have to do it manually. But takes just an hour to dry","votes":"0","username":"Red'D, Vijayawada","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"What do we have to do if length of power cord is not sufficient? How can we extend without using extension box?","answer":"If you are having good electrical knowledge, you can remove the back door and replace the entire cord from the terminal itself with a required length.","votes":"0","username":"Red'D, Vijayawada","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I schedule the installation date as per my availability?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Red'D, Vijayawada","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which year model will be delivered","answer":"The latest one, I believe","votes":"0","username":"Red'D, Vijayawada","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it require stabilizer","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Swarndeep kumar","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e4f1cfba6a7878438fd"},"product_asin":"B08SR4L6X2","QAs":[{"question":"Deos it come with outlet hose gudie ( u bend) in the box?","answer":"Flexible plastic outlet/drain pipe of 2 meter length is factory fixed for this model.","votes":"0","username":"Prashanth Narayan","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"After drying can we keep it in cupboard","answer":"No, does not have a heater drier. Hence, needs few hours of regular rope drying.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which is good in terms of RPM, 1200 or 1400?","answer":"Hi, 1200 rpm is sufficient for daily usage. Machine is just top notch. Go for it.","votes":"0","username":"Ankit","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which year model is this ?","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Ankit","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it require stand???","answer":"Yes, it is better to have one.","votes":"0","username":"Sabre71#","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e501cfba6a787843902"},"product_asin":"B08PZCS9J6","QAs":[{"question":"Tub self clean available?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Meena","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which detergent should be used? Powder or liquid? Which brand or only bosch brand???","answer":"We can use both types of detergent i.e. either powder or liquid. Detergent to be used shall be suitable for front load type of machine also","votes":"0","username":"Ajit","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it come with inbuilt  invertor?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vasu verma","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"With steam or without steam","answer":"Without steam","votes":"0","username":"alok rai","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Model Year.","answer":"We purchased this in 2021 and it was manufactured in same year. Model was introduced 2 yrs back.","votes":"0","username":"Ajit","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"I require a gst bill , how do i get it on purchase?","answer":"GST amount is indicated in bill and you can claim the same","votes":"0","username":"Ajit","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Tub material??","answer":"It is steel","votes":"0","username":"Ajit","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i get extended additional warranty of 3 years apart form 2 years manufacturing warranty toatal 2+3=5 years","answer":"Yes. Many a times BOSCH comes witj such schemes and you can avail that. I have personally availed the same scheme with 2+3 yrs warranty. The person who comes for installation will update you about omgoing warrantee schemes","votes":"0","username":"Ajit","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"What will be year manufacture of this product","answer":"I have answered this question","votes":"0","username":"Ajit","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do I get company warranty on the product","answer":"Yes. Service is also very good","votes":"0","username":"Ajit","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the  actual bee star rating of this washing machine ?","answer":"5 star","votes":"0","username":"Ajit","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we able to wash blankets & bedsheets in this 6 kg machine due to its small size?","answer":"Yes but only small and thin blankets..... We can't wash big or thick blankets, for that 8kg Bosch machine is the best and also Bosch's service is best than others.","votes":"0","username":"Aaryan Goswami","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"What does it mean by galvanized steel written in picture??","answer":"Means this steel cant get rusting easily.","votes":"0","username":"Aaryan Goswami","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Product is tested before delivery?","answer":"I don't think so but after the product got delivered the installation team first tests the product before installing and then installs it.....As I bought this 6kg but it had dents, then installation team asked me to keep or return the product and I decided to return and got money back within 3 days.","votes":"0","username":"Aaryan Goswami","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it dry clothes after wash?","answer":"Ya it dries clothes very well, it's automatic function.","votes":"0","username":"Aaryan Goswami","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e521cfba6a787843914"},"product_asin":"B08SR52BSM","QAs":[{"question":"This product use extra trolley stand","answer":"Trolley stand not required if washing machine is kept in dry area. It's required if kept in bathroom, but make sure the stand is very strong as machine is pretty heavy.","votes":"0","username":"Rohan","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please reconfirm the drum quality of the newer models, as I could see it’s galvanised steel opposed to stainless steel, quality degrade?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Dharmesh","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the breadth and length of bosch 7 kg front load wash machine?","answer":"GOOD","votes":"0","username":"Dharmesh","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the length breadth of bosch 7 kg front load wash machine?","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"Dharmesh","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there is a baby care","answer":"There is also option called as kids wear","votes":"0","username":"Nishchal MP","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e521cfba6a787843919"},"product_asin":"B00ZCJRXOK","QAs":[{"question":"Is this real drying or simply spinning at high speed to wring out moisture?","answer":"Full dry.. You can let the heat dissipate in open for 15-30 mins and keep it in the cupboard","votes":"0","username":"Kiran Koushik","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e521cfba6a78784391d"},"product_asin":"B08XMNBD3Q","QAs":[{"question":"After completion will the clothes be 80-90% dry or completly wet?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Srinu singaram","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What warranty?","answer":"2+10 YEARS","votes":"0","username":"WONDERSHOPEE","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"The weight of this product is mentioned as 60 kg on amazon while on bosch website it is given as 75.3 kg, why is there such difference?","answer":"exact weight is written bosch website","votes":"0","username":"WONDERSHOPEE","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is front load 9kg Bosch washing machine able to wash double layered double bed blankets","answer":"bosch doenot recommend, but if indian culture to be considered, you could load it","votes":"0","username":"AmazingSales17","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is front load 9kg Bosch washing machine able to wash double layered double bed blankets","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-08-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation free h","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-08-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine is compatible for Hard Water","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-08-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does washing machine has water heater?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-08-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it wash & dry","answer":"No it’s a pure Front loading washing machine.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Kunde","date":"2022-08-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e571cfba6a787843926"},"product_asin":"B08PZBZD5M","QAs":[{"question":"I have a basic tap available which we use for normal washing machine. Will that work or any extra attachment needed for this washing machine?","answer":"Hi, we have connected directly to the water tap. No attachment installed and the machine is working fine. My understanding is that, depending on the quality of the water in your supply, you may need a softening kit. In our case we did not need one.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine has stimmer?","answer":"Yes with heater","votes":"0","username":"parthi","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which series ?","answer":"Wjl series","votes":"0","username":"alok anand","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Unbox inspection included during delivery day ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"parthi","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Noise db level of this product?","answer":"almost noiseless. a very little noise might come during the spin time, other than that almost noiseless. I basically keep it in my utility balcony and almost all the time, I get to know that everything is done, at the last three beeps.","votes":"0","username":"Utsaha Ghosh","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Delay tlme available?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Utsaha Ghosh","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Any Drawbacks??","answer":"No","votes":"1","username":"indu rathee","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to use in built user?","answer":"There are many standard pre configured options available to select for washing different types of clothes.","votes":"0","username":"Noby Eldho","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Over load indication?","answer":"Yes available","votes":"0","username":"Noby Eldho","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this machine require stabliser?","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"Ajay Dutta","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the star rating of this model in 2022?","answer":"I believe it is 4 star. Please confirm with the seller.","votes":"0","username":"Noby Eldho","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is rat net available?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Customer…","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it work with low water pressure tap?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Customer…","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Elbow for securing the water drain hose, is it not part of this model? Ive not received it with my washing machine","answer":"No that is not included.","votes":"0","username":"Noby Eldho","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does installation go ahead automatically by process or do we need to call for installation ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Customer…","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this have drier","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Gowtham","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 2020 model","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Rajg","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e591cfba6a78784392e"},"product_asin":"B09KGXPHKF","QAs":[{"question":"Does it need outdoor dry after drying?","answer":"Yes obviously, no washing machine can dry cloths completely that you can directly wear it","votes":"0","username":"saurabh","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine a belt driven or direct drum driven motor??","answer":"Direct drive washing machines perform better than belt-drive washers. In addition, they lack belts and the other parts that most commonly wear down and break on belt-drive washers. Direct drive washers are also quieter, more reliable, and more energy-efficient than their belt-drive counterparts.","votes":"0","username":"Rakshit Rajput","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it resume from where it left after power cut?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Tapan M.","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this wifi enabled?","answer":"Yes.  Connect it through smart things app. You should have a wifi connection at home I guess for it.","votes":"0","username":"K2","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Inbuilt heater available","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Tapan M.","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine is noiceless","answer":"Yes, it is noiseless.","votes":"0","username":"Kamaljeet Singh","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this have laundry add option during a wash cycle?","answer":"No, not at all","votes":"0","username":"saurabh","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can you start the machine or washing cycle using smart things app on your phone?","answer":"You can't start the machine, as in power on from the app, but once it's on and connected to wifi, you can add washing cycle to it, send washing settings and control cycle","votes":"0","username":"⚡ Pushpendra Singh Patel ⚡","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this works with alexa","answer":"No, it doesn't","votes":"0","username":"⚡ Pushpendra Singh Patel ⚡","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Where we should use water filter for this product to reduce hardwater","answer":"In the inlet area or your tap","votes":"0","username":"⚡ Pushpendra Singh Patel ⚡","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we operate it with Google assistant or Alexa ?","answer":"No, you can't","votes":"0","username":"⚡ Pushpendra Singh Patel ⚡","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use surf also","answer":"Yes, both solid and liquid detergents can be usex","votes":"0","username":"⚡ Pushpendra Singh Patel ⚡","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it a dryer as well?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"⚡ Pushpendra Singh Patel ⚡","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e5e1cfba6a787843941"},"product_asin":"B0861C4YCG","QAs":[{"question":"Will it work fine if voltages drop to 180v? in my area the voltages rarely go above 200v. is voltages stabilizer needed?","answer":"I'm not the expert in this so I can just tell you that we have normal single phase electricity line and we never have faced any issue regarding power supply. So I THINK it should be working fine at your area too. The only thing to take care is, as per company's guideline, water tank should be at least 10 feels above the washing machine. But we have this just 7 feets above, still it's working fine, don't know what this can cause in future!see less","votes":"0","username":"Chintan Ranpura","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Smart check related, in description showing smart check available but installation time samsung executive said smart check not available this machine.","answer":"No there is no smart check","votes":"0","username":"varma m.","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I buy washing mechine related products from the person who is coming for installation.","answer":"Sure, but check the pricing beforehand so you are aware of the market pricing","votes":"0","username":"Nimish Gupta","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing year ...?","answer":"Dear Customer,This Model was launched in 2020 however you will get latest stock as per availability. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation or demo charge","answer":"Free, included in product price","votes":"0","username":"Nimish Gupta","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Exchange ऑफर है क्या?","answer":"Dear Customer,Exchange offer is applicable in this Model. To check the applicability please enter your area pin code and look for the offer. In case not able to find exchange offer please contact Amazon support Team for further assistance. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Motor Wattage of this washing machinr","answer":"Dear Customer,Power consumption of this washing machine model is 200-250 W having 5 star energy rating. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is wattage ?","answer":"Wattage isn't deal, it takes about double of time to wash than other brands like LG. So 5 star Samsung washing machine is actually 2 - 3 star only. Trust me still i regret with my decision to get samsung","votes":"0","username":"Kuldeep Maurya…","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which model having soft closed lid?","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. Washing machine model WA10T5260BY/TL comes with soft closing door. Model WA65T4262GG/TL comes with Tempered Glass Window which provides durability. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या आप गडचिरोली जिल्है मे डिलीव्हरी कर सकते हैं ?","answer":"Dear Customer,To check delivery of product please enter your area pin code on Amazon webpage of this Model. In case not able to check delivery option please contact Amazon support team. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Washing machine got delivered on May 7th. But no installation was done. Whom to contact for installation?","answer":"samsung customer care","votes":"0","username":"Ashish Sengar","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"GST","answer":"Dear Customer,Amazon Business provides purchasing solutions that lets registered businesses shop for business supplies on Amazon and get GST invoice and save up to 28% on business purchases. For that you need to sign up for free. For more details please contact Amazon support team. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why doesn't Samsung allow this washing machine to be kept on Washing machine stand ?","answer":"Dear Customer,This Washing machine model comes with levelling feets to provide stability while standing hence separate stand not required. However you can contact service engineer from nearest Samsung service center for further assistance regarding installation of stand. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it good for hard water wash","answer":"Dear Customer,You can wash clothes with hard water in this model. For better results you can use fabric softeners. Also it has Eco tub Clean feature. For the ultimate convenience, the Eco Tub Clean course keeps your top load washer fresh without using harsh chemicals. And it can even notify you automatically when it needs cleaning. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i get the latest manufacturing date ?","answer":"I can only tell you my experience. Got the machine on 1st Jan 2022. It was manufactured in Nov. 2021.  That seems fine. Hope it answers your query.","votes":"0","username":"Arun Kumar Malhotra","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the manufacturing date?","answer":"2020","votes":"0","username":"SOUVIK MANDAL","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it made in china?","answer":"No sir,","votes":"0","username":"SOUVIK MANDAL","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have 5.8 kg samsung washing machine working condition eligible for exchange","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"GIRIDHAR","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"I dont have tap water connection will it work?","answer":"It won't work and if you have tap water then also don't take it , it's of no use not cleaning the clothes other top load in Samsung are good but this model is pathetic","votes":"0","username":"Manas","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this model have rat mesh ?","answer":"It is covered and closed from back and bottom also.","votes":"0","username":"Ashish Sengar","date":"2022-07-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Power cut memory hai kya isme?","answer":"Dear Customer,This fully automatic washing machine model resumes cycle again after power cut. For e.g. if spin cycle was running during power cut. It will resume same cycle after power cut. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can be use in hard/salt water?","answer":"Dear Customer,You can wash clothes with hard water in this model. For better washing results you can add fabric softners. Also it has Eco tub Clean feature. For the ultimate convenience, the Eco Tub Clean course keeps your top load washer fresh without using harsh chemicals. And it can even notify you automatically when it needs cleaning. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"The material of the outer body of the machine?","answer":"Dear Customer,Outer Body is combination of high quality plastic and steel which is corrosion and rust proof. Drum is made of stainless steel. Diamond Drum’s unique “soft curl”design washes clothes very effectively,while treating them with care. Its smooth,diamond-shaped ridges are gentle on even delicate items. The small water exit holes also prevent fabric from becoming trapped and damaged. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"मेरे घर में पानी की सप्लाई सीधे नहीं तो मेरे use की है ?","answer":"Dear Customer,Direct water connection is not necessary. Basic installation requirement will be a Tap water connection which can also be connected with water tank storage. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"I dont have tap water connection will it work?","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for query. Tap connection is installation requirement for this Washing Machine model. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it work fine if voltages drop to 180v? in my area the voltages rarely go above 200v. is voltages stabilizer needed?","answer":"Dear Customer,This fully automatic Top load washing machine model has direct drive digital inverter motor hence separate stabilizer not required. However, if there is frequent voltage fluctuation please ask the service engineer regarding stabilizer at the time of installation/demo. AC 220-240 V /50Hz fuse or circuit breaker is required. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will Installation be void if i open the box by myself and install it on my own","answer":"It already, installed.","votes":"0","username":"Chirag Rawal","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e5e1cfba6a78784394c"},"product_asin":"B09KGYCR7Z","QAs":[{"question":"Can we only dry clothes without washing them in this machine?","answer":"Yes, it has a function name 'Drain/Spin' which drains all water and spins the drum at 1200 RPM","votes":"0","username":"Tejas Kapadia","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"In buit ceramic heater this washing machine","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Tejas Kapadia","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Shall we do only dry clothes in this machine ?","answer":"No, You can wash wet cloth also, but When intially system sensing more weight of wet cloth compare to  dry cloth.","votes":"0","username":"Prasanta Kumar Pradhan","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we get stand for the Washing machine","answer":"You have to purchase separate. It doesn't comes with machine.","votes":"0","username":"VICKY DAVIA","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Sound in decibles???","answer":"Almost Zero during washing but at the time of drying it has normal spinning sound because drum runs in speed.","votes":"0","username":"VICKY DAVIA","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"How does wifi work in this machine","answer":"It works pretty well, one can set the timing to run the machine and the work is automatically done .","votes":"0","username":"pradyumna","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have bubble cleaning feature , which cleans by generating foam?","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. This Washing Machine is not available with Eco Bubble Technology. It comes with AI control Washing and Hygiene Steam. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which one is better between two?","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. WW70T502NAN/TL is 2021 Model however WW70T502NAN1TL is latest 2022 Model with 5 Star energy efficiency rating. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we delay and add clothes during wash cycle","answer":"Dear Customer,Yes, delay end feature is available in this Fully automatic washing machine model .You can set the washing machine to finish your wash automatically at later time. Choose a delay of between 1 to 24 hours (in 1 hour increments). Add Wash feature is not available however you need to pause the Machine and then add additional laundry. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it EcoBubble washing?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Prem Ghanshaym Raval","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it free installation","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Prem Ghanshaym Raval","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine a wash-dryer or is it only for washing??","answer":"This is a wash-dryer machine.","votes":"0","username":"VICKY DAVIA","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing year?","answer":"Dear Customer,This model was available for purchase in 2022. You will get latest stock as per availability. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the noise level in wash and spin in this machine","answer":"Dear Customer,This Model Spin speed is 1200 RPM. It comes with digital inverter motor hence it delivers powerful but quiet cycles. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"This machine will dry clothes atleast 50% after wash?","answer":"The clothes are quite dry once out of the machine.  Even without sunlight in a dry climate, it dries in a few hours.","votes":"0","username":"A Prashanth","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"There is no exchange offer ??","answer":"It's there","votes":"0","username":"Prem Ghanshaym Raval","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to install washing machine","answer":"Dear Customer,After delivery of your Product our service support team will help with free Demo and Installation at your door step. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is inbuilt heater available","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Prem Ghanshaym Raval","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"In bilt heater???","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Prem Ghanshaym Raval","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Bubble system eneble ???","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Prem Ghanshaym Raval","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the touch panel display water proof?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"MAYANK…","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"does it need a stand?","answer":"Yes....","votes":"0","username":"VICKY DAVIA","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is wifi and non wifi in washing machine","answer":"With wifi  model you can control some basic functions from your phone directly","votes":"0","username":"MAYANK…","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many days post delivery does the installation happen","answer":"Really good working . Cost effective and more silent working machine . Really awesome","votes":"0","username":"aravindh","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the install happen with delivery?","answer":"It's depends on your location, you will get sms Or email you can call that and check when installation person coming. but with in 48hr , not same time .. Different person.. Might be same day.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"We have low water pressure in pipes as we stay in single storied house. Does the machine still work in low water pressure?","answer":"Yes it will.","votes":"0","username":"Shikhar Shrivastava","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have direct drive, i.e. no belt ?","answer":"Direct drive","votes":"0","username":"Arun Thomas","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which model has eco bubble technology","answer":"Dear Customer,You can opt for washing machine model WW70T502DAX1TL having Eco Bubble technology. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Wi fi ku Diya hua rahata hai","answer":"Dear Customer,You can connect this Washing machine with Wi-Fi through SmartThings App available in iOS and Android devices. After downloading the App select the Washing Machine to connect and start operating from your Smart phone directly. It also comes with AI control which notes your washing patterns and gives recommended Washing cycles to choose from. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"How good is this with hard water? Do we need  an additional water softener?","answer":"Dear Customer,You can use hard water for laundry washing. For best results you can use softener. It comes  Drum Clean feature keeps your front load washer fresh without using harsh chemicals. And it can even notify you automatically when it needs cleaning. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many days post delivery does the installation happen","answer":"Dear Customer,Yes, you get a call from support team for installation/demo as per convenient time and date after delivery of product. In case you haven't received call please contact our support team on toll free number 1-800-40-726-7864 (1-800-40-SAMSUNG) and Whats app number 1800-57-267864 for installation request. Usually it is done within 2-3 days  depending upon service location. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have direct drive, i.e. no belt ?","answer":"Dear Customer,This Washing machine model comes with Direct Drive Digital Inverter motor. Digital Inverter Technology utilizes strong magnets for quieter and more powerful performance, but consumes less energy than a Universal Motor. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e601cfba6a787843958"},"product_asin":"B099GLFH5T","QAs":[{"question":"Can i wash shoes in this machine??","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. Washing shoes not recommended, it is suitable for laundry washing. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many units of power consumption is daily estimated for a solid 1hr program?","answer":"Dear Customer,This 5 Star rated washing machine model energy consumption is 0.0115 kWh/kg/cycle. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"This body is metal or plastic?","answer":"Metal. But the top cover is plastic + glass","votes":"0","username":"Raghu Krishnan","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Who to meet if washing machine get in problem after buying","answer":"Samsung service","votes":"0","username":"Raghu Krishnan","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine rat free?","answer":"Yes it is. Machine has a preventable rat frame installed at the bottom of the washing machine","votes":"0","username":"Vipul","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"This machine 's power  wattage of motor?","answer":"500 watt overall machine wattage","votes":"0","username":"chandan","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"inlet pipe is available or not,","answer":"Yes comes with machine","votes":"0","username":"chandan","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"When i got refund of cancelled items","answer":"Please connect custmor care","votes":"0","username":"chandan","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will the steel body perish quickly?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"chandan","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will the steel body perish quickly?","answer":"Dear Customer,This Washing Machine model comes with combination of metal and high grade plastic on outer body. The body is designed for long lasting durability Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"This machine 's power  wattage of motor?","answer":"Dear Customer,Maximum power consumption of this Washing machine is 500W. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e631cfba6a787843965"},"product_asin":"B08779BJY1","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have soft closing door?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Aldrin D'Souza","date":"2022-06-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"model year","answer":"2020","votes":"0","username":"Aldrin D'Souza","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use pale water for washing","answer":"Not recommended","votes":"0","username":"Amitabh Talwar","date":"2022-06-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which year manufacturing is this?","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Aldrin D'Souza","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e681cfba6a787843983"},"product_asin":"B08GXYZFNB","QAs":[{"question":"Product ki height kitni h","answer":"Dear Customer,Net dimension (WxHxD) cm of this model is 54 x 92.6 x 56.8 cm. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Outer body is aluminium or plactic?","answer":"Dear Customer,Outer body is high grade plastic with inner steel frame. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which material is used as anti rat cover?","answer":"Dear Customer,Anti rat cover is made of high-grade plastic . Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e6a1cfba6a787843987"},"product_asin":"B08KTKH5K4","QAs":[{"question":"Can I pour water in it manually??","answer":"Yes. You can","votes":"0","username":"Prafull Mataghare","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this product have auto restart function?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Shaik Abdul Rahiman-Kurnoolian","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"model year","answer":"If you want to buy this you should have another Rs.15000 to buy a UPS. Otherwise there will be a problem.","votes":"0","username":"pedar","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"If at all Power failure the wm will restart from the stop time or from the beginning","answer":"I tried for a solution. There is no proper answer from the company and also Amazon also left it at that stage.","votes":"0","username":"pedar","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installing free???","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Prafull Mataghare","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have hydrolic door ?","answer":"Spring are attached to door.","votes":"0","username":"Prafull Mataghare","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any settings for quick wash like 30 mins??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Prafull Mataghare","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e6c1cfba6a787843990"},"product_asin":"B09BR9NQ37","QAs":[{"question":"how rinsing done.Is there water changeover knob from washer tub to spin drier tub ?","answer":"Not so good","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e6d1cfba6a787843992"},"product_asin":"B087795NDB","QAs":[{"question":"Iska jo shutter he wo hidrolic he ?","answer":"Yes it's hydrolic and works very good","votes":"0","username":"Rahul Bihani , Loni","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i wash double blanket?","answer":"we haven't tried either double or single blanket but double comforter which is lighter can be washed and dried pretty well. I would say better not to try blankets as they become very heavy after soaking up water","votes":"0","username":"Indrashish Sengupta","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e701cfba6a78784399a"},"product_asin":"B08WX2LSP4","QAs":[{"question":"How many litres of water will it get maximum ?","answer":"Not sure about that. But experience with this washing machine is very bad. It does not clean the cloths properly even after two cycles. Samsung did not provided any satisfactory solution at all.","votes":"0","username":"Dharamjeet Singh","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do this work on 1000 volt sollar plat","answer":"Dear Customer,Voltage/Frequency requirement of this Washing machine model is 230V / 50Hz hence it should work however please check from service engineer at the time of installation. Power consumption of this washing machine is 200-250 W. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this washing machine  fiber body","answer":"Dear Customer,The outer body of this washing machine is made of high quality plastic material. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to remove rhe enlarged sink tray?","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. The Active Wash+ feature sink is non-removable. This sink provides a convenient place to hand-wash delicate items and pre-treat heavily soiled clothes. A water jet starts and stops at the push of a button. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"is there spin only function","answer":"Yes, only spin can be done but its a bit tricky. You need to manipulate the settings. Direct only spon not avlbl","votes":"0","username":"Shek Pals","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Wouldn't it be a problem to use it in salt water?","answer":"Should not be a prob","votes":"0","username":"Shek Pals","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"How we connect water for this type washing machine","answer":"You need a half 8nch tap adapter","votes":"0","username":"Shek Pals","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya is mein blanket wash mode hai","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. This model is not available with Blanket Wash Mode. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this machine have Auto restart facility","answer":"Well, once you choose the required washing cycle within the options provided you have to start the machine yourself in the beginning and the machine does the work for you. You are liberted to start/pause the cycle during the washing process except while draining (option automatically gets disabled). In any event it will not autorestart if interrupted manually or due to external factors (power cut).see less","votes":"0","username":"Sylivya…","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Washing machine is taking more than sufficient water what to do anyone help pls??","answer":"The machine's water intake capacity is upto level 5. You can repeatedly press the water level button to change the level as per your convenience even if the machine autoselects any particular level (which it does depending on the load)","votes":"0","username":"Sylivya…","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Rat mesh ?","answer":"Provided along","votes":"0","username":"Sylivya…","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Wouldn't it be a problem to use it in salt water?","answer":"Dear Customer,You can wash clothes with hard water in this model. For better results you can use fabric softeners. Also it has Drum Clean feature. For the ultimate convenience, the Drum Clean Clean course keeps your top load washer fresh without using harsh chemicals. And it can even notify you automatically when it needs cleaning. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"is there spin only function","answer":"Dear Customer,Through option list you can select Spin cycle by manual selection. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this machine have Auto restart facility","answer":"Dear Customer,This fully automatic washing machine model resumes cycle again after power cut. For e.g. if spin cycle was running during power cut. It will resume same cycle after power cut. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e731cfba6a7878439bc"},"product_asin":"B08ZJHJ5DJ","QAs":[{"question":"Is plastic cover for washing machine","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"D","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Plastic back or stainless steal?","answer":"Plastic back","votes":"0","username":"Arnab Chakraborty","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much charges take to installation ?","answer":"Free installation","votes":"0","username":"Arnab Chakraborty","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much energy star rating?","answer":"See product details","votes":"0","username":"Arnab Chakraborty","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Panch member ke liye kafi hai","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Arnab Chakraborty","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Smart door?","answer":"See product details","votes":"0","username":"Arnab Chakraborty","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation is free or chargeble","answer":"Free","votes":"0","username":"Arnab Chakraborty","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e791cfba6a7878439e5"},"product_asin":"B082GFNRKM","QAs":[{"question":"Does this model have led display timer?","answer":"Yes,","votes":"0","username":"S.Sathiskumar","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e7f1cfba6a787843a15"},"product_asin":"B082FJ9RS7","QAs":[{"question":"Year of manufacturing","answer":"2020","votes":"0","username":"Prabakaran.N","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has child lock and sensing ?","answer":"Might be","votes":"0","username":"Praveen Kurup","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e7f1cfba6a787843a17"},"product_asin":"B095PT9K7Z","QAs":[{"question":"Guarantee? Warranty?","answer":"Really good , excellent after sales support .","votes":"0","username":"Prabhushankar","date":"2022-07-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e851cfba6a787843a23"},"product_asin":"B082FJMJNN","QAs":[{"question":"Should we purchse the extra powder packets for cleaning the drum?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Burhan Lone","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I connect this washing machine with alexa ?","answer":"For now technology is in Japan only, when comes to india Alexa will put clothes too","votes":"0","username":"varun shrivastava","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this model had anti clock feature or not???","answer":"360","votes":"0","username":"varun shrivastava","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hey, I don't see my warranty card. What's the best way to get the customer service with a potential issue? The machine is only 6 months old","answer":"Amazon should refer this question to manufacturers asking fellow customer is like indirectly protecting manufacturer .","votes":"0","username":"SUNILBAJAJ","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Auto restart option is available or not?","answer":"yes available","votes":"0","username":"Shaik Naina","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"During installation service agent asked us to put scalegon and calstarit  . Is that necessary? With charge","answer":"not asking","votes":"0","username":"Shaik Naina","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manually bucket water fill","answer":"Yes. but this one is fully automatic","votes":"0","username":"Shaik Naina","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Machine ka weight kitna h","answer":"24 kg","votes":"0","username":"varun shrivastava","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there delivery of washing machine in karnal city?","answer":"check your pincode","votes":"0","username":"Shaik Naina","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we start where it stopp","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Shaik Naina","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the difference between automatic & semiautomatic washing machine","answer":"Semi-automatic mein sab khud karna padta hai...button settings...water fill.","votes":"0","username":"varun shrivastava","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"with this price installation will be done and who will do it","answer":"Company service man and free of cost","votes":"0","username":"varun shrivastava","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much liter of water required in 1 wash","answer":"10-12 ltrs","votes":"0","username":"varun shrivastava","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Motor speed?","answer":"Very fast","votes":"0","username":"varun shrivastava","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many years warranty for whole product, on motor and and compressor","answer":"5 years","votes":"0","username":"varun shrivastava","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warenty period","answer":"5 years","votes":"0","username":"varun shrivastava","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it contain dryer??","answer":"Yes it's fully automatic","votes":"0","username":"varun shrivastava","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e871cfba6a787843a4d"},"product_asin":"B07BNLKS7V","QAs":[{"question":"Modle of which year","answer":"i think its 2021 was i order","votes":"0","username":"Murale shankar B","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"both Motor  warranty for 10 year na","answer":"Nope , primary washing moter will be cover 10yr and secondary dryer moter cover only 2 year . Solid built so mostly sooner may not come moter issue","votes":"0","username":"Murale shankar B","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e881cfba6a787843a50"},"product_asin":"B08L5CRR6R","QAs":[{"question":"Rat protection is there","answer":"It's hard, but","votes":"0","username":"Somprasad Poudel","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"can we wash saree ?","answer":"Yes we can wash.","votes":"0","username":"Somprasad Poudel","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Mottor Warranty ?","answer":"2 Years Comprehensive Warranty on Product and 10 Years on Wash Motor and Prime Mover.","votes":"0","username":"Somprasad Poudel","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87e911cfba6a787843a9d"},"product_asin":"B083G25P9L","QAs":[{"question":"Is the body made of metal or fiber/plastic?","answer":"Plastic","votes":"0","username":"aditya sikarwar","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have lint collector ?","answer":"Yes. It has","votes":"0","username":"Bhargava","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"I can use king size bed sheets for wash through this machine","answer":"Yes. But the quality of washing won't be too good.","votes":"0","username":"ARINDAM DUTTA","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"who does the installation? can it be installed by own?","answer":"Yes you can easily, don't rely on company technician. They are not useful. You go through the guide and do it on your own.","votes":"0","username":"P V Prasad","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"clothes are not getting dried properly","answer":"Yes, but check the level. You fill dryer up to 75 pc and then try. If you fill totally with clothes it generates huge sound.","votes":"0","username":"P V Prasad","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"warranty of the product","answer":"One'year","votes":"0","username":"P V Prasad","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can u tell me This washing machine work with out over head tank?","answer":"Yes it will work without water storage tank, but u need water to wash the clothes which u can easily store in the machine itself,","votes":"0","username":"Rizwan patel","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Capacity of spin tub","answer":"Depends. My machine is 7 kg","votes":"0","username":"P V Prasad","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Purani washing machine exange ho sakti h kya","answer":"Depends","votes":"0","username":"P V Prasad","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"I ordered this machine  but my sim card is not working and i want to change my number for received my product","answer":"You contact Amazon customer care and change your mobile number","votes":"0","username":"P V Prasad","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"My washing machine's Inbuilt scrubber is damaged, can I replace it with a new one, if yes where can I buy it?","answer":"Contact service centre, they will change","votes":"0","username":"P V Prasad","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Had ordered this product and recived as per schedule but if installation demo is needed whom to contact?","answer":"Company service technician, send a mail or contact Amazon customer care if you had purchased the product from them","votes":"0","username":"P V Prasad","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there a return policy available for this product?","answer":"I don't think, it is only replaceable in case any manufacturing defect","votes":"0","username":"P V Prasad","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"At the end it do any sound like buzzer","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"aditya sikarwar","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we need water softner with semi automatic machine","answer":"Only if you are going to use hard water orelse water softner is not required.....vineger is best if you use hard water","votes":"0","username":"Devang Kadakia","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87eb41cfba6a787843b7a"},"product_asin":"B08KRZ69XY","QAs":[{"question":"Is display pannel waterproof","answer":"Yes, display panel is waterproof","votes":"0","username":"WONDERSHOPEE","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"In this machine have inbuilt heater","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amarjit Singh","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the difference between Waj2846sin and  Waj28262in?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amarjit Singh","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it spin only?","answer":"wash and spin both","votes":"0","username":"WONDERSHOPEE","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87eb41cfba6a787843b7e"},"product_asin":"B08KTL8FDF","QAs":[{"question":"what is the power cord length","answer":"4.5 feet and the insertion is at the bottom left corner when you look at it from the back side","votes":"0","username":"WONDERSHOPEE","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this having dryer?","answer":"Yes, this model contains both Washing & Dryer facility in it.","votes":"0","username":"WONDERSHOPEE","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cord length","answer":"4.5 feet and the insertion is at the bottom left corner when you look at it from the back side.","votes":"0","username":"Main Pal","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87eb41cfba6a787843b84"},"product_asin":"B08SR5BPLK","QAs":[{"question":"Can we add clothes midcycle ?","answer":"YES","votes":"0","username":"Arunachalam","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Upto how many days after receiving the product i can return it if i find any faults?? Please reoly fast i m gonna buy a washing machine today.","answer":"10 days","votes":"0","username":"Arunachalam","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use normal detergent/surf like tide, surf excel etc  ??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Suresh Chandra M","date":"2022-06-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do you install it in Coimbatore?","answer":"In Bangalore","votes":"0","username":"Ananth Nagesh","date":"2022-06-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this having eco silence drive","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Suresh Chandra M","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I use liquid detergent","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Suresh Chandra M","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have 61 cm gap into which the machine should go.  one reviewer mentioned the width is 61.5 cm.  what is exact width ?","answer":"61.5 is a safer bet but you can check dimensions before buying","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Lot of customer reviews it was broken","answer":"Had no such problem","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we pay through bajaj finance","answer":"Why not","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which ditergent can we use in this machine","answer":"Surf excel matic powder or liquid","votes":"0","username":"RAMESH BABU  BURAGA","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it have auto cleaning procedure","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Automatically dary?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"NAVANEETHAM S.","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can you confirm warranty, on othet side same model has 3 years?","answer":"1 yr","votes":"0","username":"NAVANEETHAM S.","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87eb61cfba6a787843b90"},"product_asin":"B09KGW3NWL","QAs":[{"question":"What metal is its drum made of?","answer":"Stainless-steel","votes":"0","username":"Manish Mauta","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the colour of lid ?","answer":"Dear Customer,Body color of this Washing Machine is White and Door Color (Lid) is Black. Please check product main Image showing color details. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Lid colour is black or white ?","answer":"Dear Customer,Body color of this Washing Machine is White and Door Color (Lid) is Black. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"hi, can you provide installation service in Aizawl, Mizoram?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"salim shaikh","date":"2022-08-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it need stabilizer?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"salim shaikh","date":"2022-08-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87eb81cfba6a787843b99"},"product_asin":"B08HZ5XQD3","QAs":[{"question":"model manufacturing year","answer":"2019","votes":"0","username":"Wg. Cdr. Alok Kaushal (Retd)","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"what are samsung washing machine models with automatic and non inverter?","answer":"Wa65a4022ns","votes":"0","username":"Sun Enterprise Vadodara","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Witch as real prise in samsung dimond drupm 6.5 kg washing mashin","answer":"Prices are changing day to day. You can get same item at low cost as you see today.","votes":"0","username":"sunilsingh","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87eb91cfba6a787843ba0"},"product_asin":"B09KGY7S81","QAs":[{"question":"Can we only dry clothes without washing them in this machine","answer":"Yes, you can.","votes":"0","username":"Jayshree d.","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which year model is this?","answer":"2022 this may 22nd model","votes":"0","username":"DEVAN","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the difference between net dimension and product diamension, your team making total confusion","answer":"मुझे समझ नही आया आप फोन कर सकते है","votes":"0","username":"Rahul Patidar","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the actual   dimension of ww70t4020ee1tl","answer":"Simply super... quality is excellent","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there only Spin function in this machine means if I want to spin the clothes only is it possible","answer":"Yes there is a drier option is there.","votes":"0","username":"Tirumalesh S","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Auto restart is there","answer":"Yes in case of power cut it will resume from last left time.","votes":"0","username":"Neeraj Rautela","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this machine stop when water is not available and resume when water becomes available?","answer":"When water is not available it will throw an error and stop washing the cloth.","votes":"0","username":"Neeraj Rautela","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the minimum water pressure required?","answer":"normal pressure","votes":"0","username":"Rupesh Sharma","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is direct drive?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amarnath","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it belt driven or shaft driven?","answer":"It’s direct drive","votes":"0","username":"Amarnath","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"[wronginfo] how can the lxwxh is in 5.5x6x8.9 meters ? i mean in meter ?","answer":"I think in feets.","votes":"-1","username":"Tirumalesh S","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does 2022 model have ecobubble?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"NAVEEN KUMAR","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What kind of drives ?....belt drive or direct drive","answer":"Direct drive","votes":"0","username":"Amarnath","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is smart check option available with this modeland how does this feature works?","answer":"Based on weight of the cloths and it indicates some signs on display with red.","votes":"0","username":"Tirumalesh S","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hot water inbuilt heater is available","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Tirumalesh S","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this product have 5 star ratings ?","answer":"Dear Customer,Washing machine Model WW70T4020EE1TL comes with 5 Star Energy efficiency and digital inverter motor. DIT offers less noise and a long-lasting performance. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we adjust duration of soaking?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to find 2022 and 2021 model  different","answer":"It is available at description and specifications","votes":"0","username":"Tirumalesh S","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Motor warranty and product warranty?","answer":"Motor I think 3yrs and product is 1yr","votes":"0","username":"Tirumalesh S","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i set the cycle for 30mins","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Tirumalesh S","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is difference in front lod and top load","answer":"Please Google it","votes":"0","username":"Tirumalesh S","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ebb1cfba6a787843bac"},"product_asin":"B09KGVKZXS","QAs":[{"question":"Is there pause and add feature","answer":"Yes ,it has..","votes":"0","username":"Hemanth Kumar","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Touch panel?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ceramic coated heater there or not","answer":"Dear Customer,Yes, Ceramic heater is available in this Washing machine model. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it display load?","answer":"Dear Customer,Once you set the cycle you want, the screen displays a brief cycle description, maximum laundry load, and cycle time. You can also check the cycle progress, remaining cycle time, and information codes. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use without wifi connection","answer":"Yes brother","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this work on house inverter","answer":"Dear Customer,Power consumption (Washing and heating) of this Washing machine model is 1900-2300 W. Hence it is advisable to not use with Home Inverter. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine a belt driven or direct driven motor?","answer":"Dear Customer,This model comes with direct drive digital inverter motor. Digital Inverter Technology utilizes strong magnets for a quieter and more powerful performance, but consumes less energy than a Universal Motor. By eliminating the use of brushes, it provides outstanding durability – backed-up by a 10 year warranty. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i operate it without using phone also ?","answer":"Yes it can be . One of the best washing machine.","votes":"0","username":"vinay","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"In built heater is there","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"vinay","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there a notification of wash cycle end in SmartThings app","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sameer","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there steam washing mode?","answer":"S","votes":"0","username":"M RAJ KUMAR","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can this washing machine removes stains on collar?","answer":"S,i have checked twice... It is working good","votes":"0","username":"M RAJ KUMAR","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this 1400 rpm or 1200 rpm?.. You mentioned 2 rpms","answer":"1400 max","votes":"0","username":"Sameer","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Howmany was programs?","answer":"21","votes":"0","username":"Harshith Yechuri","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it comes with Rat mesh?","answer":"Yes and washing quality super like hand wash","votes":"0","username":"manikandan","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it require stabilizer?","answer":"No needed because you are not using 24/7","votes":"0","username":"manikandan","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Noise in db","answer":"I am not sure but very less noises compared others","votes":"0","username":"manikandan","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"where is this product built? How about the spare part support?","answer":"Every thing good","votes":"0","username":"manikandan","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there an auto restart feature?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"manikandan","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this 2022  model","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Chandrasekhar","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"It has ecobubble technologh or not","answer":"Yes it has ecobubble technology.","votes":"0","username":"Chandrasekhar","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be installed on a stand ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Chandrasekhar","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty provided by Amazon or Samsung","answer":"Warranty  and service also provided by Samsung only","votes":"0","username":"Nani","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ebc1cfba6a787843bc1"},"product_asin":"B084LGQKD7","QAs":[{"question":"Is it having dryer with Iron?","answer":"It has a dryer, which dries up to 90%. There is no washing machine which irons.","votes":"0","username":"Dr.Kantilal J.","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"My clothes are damp after all kinds of different cycles. How do I change the settings to make them fully dry ?","answer":"No machine dries 100%. Try setting the dryer RPM to 1000 cycles per minute","votes":"0","username":"Dr.Kantilal J.","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there a inbuilt water softener for hard water wash? Or is it recommended to use a external water softener?","answer":"These are baseless questions which I donot think any relevant if you have a free flowing water then these things donot come up","votes":"0","username":"Saugata Roy Choudhury","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there a facility to soften water/treat hard/salt water in built? If not what other options do I need externally to ensure good maintenance? Thanks","answer":"Dear Customer,You can use hard water in this Washing machine model with softener for best results. Also clean the drum with dry cloth once washing cycle is complete. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Volume of the tank","answer":"Dear Customer,Washing Capacity of this Washing Machine model is 6.0 kg. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"I do not have a power socket near where I can keep the washing machine. Will this machine work if I use an extension cable?","answer":"Dear Customer,You can use extension cord however it is advisable to not use any other appliance in the cord when using Washing Machine. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we have to plug direct to the wall power socket or can we use plug it to the extension?","answer":"Dear Customer,In case the power socket is far from Installation site of Washing Machine you can use extension cord however it is advisable to not use any other appliance in the cord when using Washing Machine. Best will be to use with power socket directly. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Inverter pcb under guarantee?","answer":"Dear Customer,You will get 3 years comprehensive warranty on product which include internal parts and 10 years warranty on motor from Samsung India. Onsite warranty will be available with this product. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"This product is which year of manufacturer ?? Also when is available 2022 year manufacturer model ??","answer":"Dear Customer,This Model was launched in 2020 however you will get latest model as per availability. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is wattage?","answer":"0.09 wts/kg/cycle","votes":"0","username":"venkatarao","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"5amo/15amp","answer":"15 amp","votes":"0","username":"Dr.Kantilal J.","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do the clothes tear in the drum?","answer":"No. So far never happened. We used regular n formal wear...All r good","votes":"0","username":"venkatarao","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have a place to put conditioner ?","answer":"Dear Customer,Yes, This washing machine model comes with a detergent and softener compartment.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we wash through cold water in cotton cycle","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Saugata Roy Choudhury","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use ground water for washing clothes in this machine","answer":"You should have an inlet","votes":"0","username":"Saugata Roy Choudhury","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Motor will made by copper or silver?","answer":"Copper","votes":"0","username":"Saugata Roy Choudhury","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"In which compartment to insert liquid detergent?? In main wash or prewash","answer":"Main wash","votes":"0","username":"Dr.Kantilal J.","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Shiping charges","answer":"Free","votes":"0","username":"Dr.Kantilal J.","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the difference from similar model (newer and bit expensive) starting with WW61?","answer":"Dear Customer,You can check and compare feature of both models through Samsung India official webpage. However both are 5 Star Rated and comes in 6 kg Capacity. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"मशीन में सर्विस की जरूरत","answer":"In 2 years, I needed to get service once and that was a small issue due to hard water quality at my place.","votes":"0","username":"priyanshu daksha","date":"2022-07-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is a spin cancel option available?","answer":"Spin is an integral part of wash, used to wring the clothes of detergent. It cannot be cancelled. However, the spin in the last cycle of wash, which is for drying, can be cancelled before you start the wash.","votes":"0","username":"Dr.Kantilal J.","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is cremaic heater a coted one?","answer":"Yes ceramic coated heater, so scaling of the heating element by hard water is minimized.","votes":"0","username":"Dr.Kantilal J.","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much litres of water required to wash fifteen clothes","answer":"The load is calculated in kgs, not number of clothes. For a load of 6 kgs, it takes 35 to 45 liters, depending upon the wash cycle chosen.","votes":"0","username":"Dr.Kantilal J.","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"This machine have a try wash","answer":"You mean, dry wash?","votes":"0","username":"Dr.Kantilal J.","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there a inbuilt water softener for hard water wash? Or is it recommended to use a external water softener?","answer":"Dear Customer,You can wash clothes in hard water. To make washing efficient you can add softeners. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this washing machine have Self tub cleaning feature?","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. This Washing machine model is not available with Drum Clean feature. You can opt for model WW70T4020EE1TL having a drum clean feature. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How do I know where to use liquid detergent and powder out of three partion trays","answer":"In left large compartment","votes":"0","username":"Dr.Kantilal J.","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing year?","answer":"Dear Customer,This Model is available since 2020 however you will get latest model as per the availability. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is a spin cancel option available?","answer":"Dear Customer,To cancel spin cycle press spin button till it shows light on stop spin cycle icon. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much litres of water required to wash fifteen clothes","answer":"Dear Customer,This fully automatic Front load washing machine water consumption is ~55L (for cotton course). [ for max loading: 6kg*9L = 54L ] Rest will vary depending on load and course. In general, water and energy consumption is more efficient (lesser) than top loading and semi automatic machines. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to use and how it’s work washing machine","answer":"Dear Customer,Onsite Installation/Demo will be provided by service engineer. Also it comes with user manual which you can refer while operating. It comes with 11 cycles depending washing type required. Cycles are  15' Quick Wash , Cotton, Daily Wash, Delicates, Denim, Hygiene Steam, Option List (Pre Wash, Intensive, Rinse+), Rinse + Spin, Spin, Synthetics and wool. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"This machine have a try wash","answer":"Dear Customer,This fully automatic front load washing machine has 11 cycles depending washing type required. Cycles are  15' Quick Wash , Cotton, Daily Wash, Delicates, Denim, Hygiene Steam, Option List (Pre Wash, Intensive, Rinse+), Rinse + Spin, Spin, Synthetics and wool. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it having dryer with Iron?","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. This washing machine model is not available with Dryer with iron. There is Spin cycle available to remove moisture from clothes.  Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ebe1cfba6a787843be9"},"product_asin":"B09T6NX8W2","QAs":[{"question":"What is mator wattage  use in it","answer":"500 W","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kiya eski moter copper ki hai","answer":"पता नहीं।","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya macanic bhi aayega fiting kane ghar pe","answer":"Fitting ya installation ki koi zaroorat nahi hai. Machine aapke paas puri tarike se ready deliver hogi, aapko sirf chalana hai","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will the product be installed as well?","answer":"Installation nit required, plug it and use","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Fibralon body","answer":"Fibre body","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ebe1cfba6a787843bef"},"product_asin":"B08ZJJZDMP","QAs":[{"question":"Alaram is there  after washing completion","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Mohit Agarwal","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"model year","answer":"2022","votes":"0","username":"Sk","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation is free??","answer":"Free","votes":"0","username":"Sk","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ebf1cfba6a787843bf7"},"product_asin":"B08QNZTQ96","QAs":[{"question":"How much time it takes un quick wash","answer":"Around 35 min for normal dirty clothes","votes":"0","username":"BIKRAM SABAT","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its Airdrier mation","answer":"It's purely bad product. Functions not working properly. Making lot of sound. I'm not able to contact service people as well. Machine not taking","votes":"0","username":"Sushil Kaushik","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to contact customer care ?","answer":"I'm not able to connect customer care as well","votes":"0","username":"Sushil Kaushik","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"For emi ,initially we should pay anything?","answer":"Emi and all ok","votes":"0","username":"Sushil Kaushik","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this a invertor motor washing machine","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sushil Kaushik","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Exchange offer at burdwan golapbag available or not??","answer":"Not available","votes":"0","username":"Sushil Kaushik","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will I get the latest 2022 model?","answer":"Check with Amazon","votes":"0","username":"Avenger…","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"One year extended warranty available after delivery","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Jaganathan","date":"2022-08-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ec21cfba6a787843c0f"},"product_asin":"B07NXCK997","QAs":[{"question":"How many Watt?","answer":"360watt","votes":"0","username":"Vivian Andrew","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we dry the cloths with heat?","answer":"No only rinse n spin u need to dry outside which will dry in an hour depend on weather conditions, heater is to heat the water for washing","votes":"0","username":"Vivian Andrew","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Steel or Stainless steel material drum?","answer":"Stainless steel drum","votes":"0","username":"Vivian Andrew","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i wash hand made blanket?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vivian Andrew","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Any type of detergent used","answer":"Yes u can use any type detergent liquid","votes":"0","username":"Naga Niranjan rao","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to use in detail","answer":"U can goto whirlpool website and from there download the manuals or check whirlpool youtube channel they hav posted videos showing how to use","votes":"0","username":"Vivian Andrew","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"If we get any damage within 2 years how can we claim warrenty","answer":"Just contact the service centre they will come to home n will replace the damaged part","votes":"0","username":"Vivian Andrew","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to use in detail","answer":"It works as normal refrigerator. Nothing special in operation","votes":"0","username":"K N Jha","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the model no ?","answer":"Mentioned in the decription","votes":"0","username":"Anant Chaturvedi","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"manufacturing 2022?","answer":"No, Manufacturing year is 2021","votes":"0","username":"Anant Chaturvedi","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ec81cfba6a787843c26"},"product_asin":"B08SMC7R5S","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have wheels","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Akash Anand","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ec91cfba6a787843c34"},"product_asin":"B08CN7RZ6R","QAs":[{"question":"How can i assure that hydrilic window or top is opening ?","answer":"I assured","votes":"0","username":"Lokendra Pal Singh","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ed01cfba6a787843c55"},"product_asin":"B08L3HH6SC","QAs":[{"question":"Pause & reload option available?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sanjeev Kumar Joshi","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the percentage of drying? Does it dry clothes 100%?","answer":"60% to 70% in case of cotton or mix clothes","votes":"0","username":"sumit","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it with inverter technology ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"sumit","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ed21cfba6a787843c65"},"product_asin":"B08DDTG2XX","QAs":[{"question":"Do we have to use descaller powder to  clean the drum","answer":"Use vinegar for drum cleaning","votes":"0","username":"Sk","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it Direct drive or belt drive?","answer":"Belt","votes":"0","username":"Sk","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this washing machine have self tub clean feature?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Wash type tumble or pulsator?","answer":"Tumble","votes":"0","username":"Sk","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it restart from where it stopped when power restored?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amrik S.","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is minimum water pressure required at Inlet of the Washing m/c?","answer":"Water inlet will be of normal pressure & the machine will take the desired quantity automatically","votes":"0","username":"P GNANESWAR RAO","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"[wronginfo] the dimensions in images is lxw is 45x60 which is increased to 56x60 in the details below, what actually is the dimension ??","answer":"45×60","votes":"0","username":"N.Bhaskar","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What kind water supply require","answer":"Soft water is good but still hard water will work. Proper cleaning is required due to scaling","votes":"0","username":"P GNANESWAR RAO","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it available hot water system?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"P GNANESWAR RAO","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will i get samsung warranty card while delivery","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"P GNANESWAR RAO","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whether instalation  will be done","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"P GNANESWAR RAO","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ed31cfba6a787843c71"},"product_asin":"B08GY3PZQF","QAs":[{"question":"Is installation included?","answer":"Yes of course.","votes":"0","username":"Arindam","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Samsung service man told me to don't use trolley. If i use trolley and machine get some problem it will out of warranty.","answer":"Spinning problem","votes":"0","username":"ilu naidu","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Emi pe kaise le","answer":"Credit Card ya debit card ley saktey hoo","votes":"0","username":"Nikhil Sharma","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we move it easily from one place to another one","answer":"You should buy wheel stand.","votes":"0","username":"vinod","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"This washing machine have waterfall function","answer":"Credit card ya debit card ley saktey hoo","votes":"0","username":"Nikhil Sharma","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it also has dryer ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Shoneit","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"How long is the power chord","answer":"As long as it’s required. Standard length.","votes":"0","username":"Arindam","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine suitable for jeans , blanket, sweater . If yes, which progrrmme should we select ?? Plzz reply","answer":"Dear Customer,You can wash Blanket, Jeans, Cotton etc fabrics laundry in this Top Load Washing machine model. You can select normal wash cycle for same. For fabrics like Wool, Silk, Linen and embroidery you can choose delicate wash cycle for best results. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is tub stainless steel?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Akash Singh…","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the name of center part inside the drum?","answer":"Dear Customer,This Washing Machine Model comes with Center Jet Pulsator. Jets of water generating from the center of the pulsator which improves washing effectiveness by lifting any clothes that falls down onto the surface of the pulsator and thus preventing tangled laundry. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"This model Have wobble technology or not?","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. This Washing machine is not available with Wobble Technology. It comes with Center Jet Pulsator. Jets of water generating from the center of the pulsator which improves washing effectiveness by lifting any clothes that falls down onto the surface of the pulsator and thus preventing tangled laundry. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much time it will take for normal wash in samsung auto washing machine, for me it will take 90 minutes","answer":"Superb 👍 very good 😊👍","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"It will dry clothes automatically after washing?","answer":"The machine will only rinse your clothes. You need to hang them up for drying.","votes":"0","username":"Arindam","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i open lid in middle of a cycle ?","answer":"Yes, you can.","votes":"0","username":"akshay s.","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this machine dries clothes completely","answer":"No, upto 90%","votes":"0","username":"akshay s.","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Exchang offer","answer":"Superb 👌 thank u","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will they provide extra length of inlet and oulet pipe if required.. During installation","answer":"They supply a fixed length (maybe 1.5 mt). The person coming to install can get you longer pipes for water inlet and waste water outflow too. Excellent product and service!","votes":"0","username":"Alok Shukla","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I run this refrigerator on 200ah battery with 900va Inverter?","answer":"Thanks 👍 superb","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the size of washing machine tub?","answer":"20L","votes":"0","username":"akshay s.","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing date?","answer":"I recently bought this machine it’s been 15 days working perfectly, good quality as expected just go for it.","votes":"0","username":"Devender","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it Samsung wooble technology","answer":"I dont know. But dont buy samsung product at all. The service is beyond sadness. Installation will happen at the speed of SBI Loan process","votes":"0","username":"Raju Bohora","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to claim warrenty in case of motor fault?","answer":"Dear Customer,You can claim warranty through Electronic Bill received on Email/Hard Copy received with product, warranty can be claimed from nearest Samsung authorized service center or call our support team on toll free number 1800-40-7267864 and whats app number 1800-5-7267864. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the machine water resistant?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i get it delivered in different city and installation in different city?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What will be total warranty of motor? 4 year?s","answer":"Dear Customer,You will get 2 Year comprehensive warranty on product which includes motor warranty. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we get till 10th of may pin vode 444001?","answer":"Superb 👍 thank you","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Any hidden charges?","answer":"Hidden sadness? Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Raju Bohora","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Delivery to 416114","answer":"Superb","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"can i turn off somehow this beep sound in the end of washing? I don't want to hear this sound","answer":"Use cotton","votes":"0","username":"Snigdha Sajal Das","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is procedure for machine service","answer":"Contact Customer care","votes":"0","username":"Snigdha Sajal Das","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Who will delivered this product delivery partners like (Ecom , Delivery) or Amazon","answer":"Concrete on product not delivery partner","votes":"0","username":"Snigdha Sajal Das","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can someone tell me how it is used in brief??? And does it also dry the clothes or how is it done ?","answer":"Dryer is good but you have to expose to o open air 4 to five hours, in direct Sun light one two two hours. Buy it and experience the   process very simple no rocket science.","votes":"0","username":"Snigdha Sajal Das","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the Energy rating of this product?","answer":"3star","votes":"0","username":"Arun","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it working in low water presure","answer":"May be","votes":"0","username":"Snigdha Sajal Das","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the total warranty on motor? at some places, it is 10 years and at others, it is just 2 years. whom to believe.","answer":"Let them stamp the warranty card first","votes":"0","username":"Raju Bohora","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty period is not mentioned on warranty card","answer":"Superb 👍 thank you","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this model can work if select only Wash and rinse?","answer":"May be","votes":"0","username":"Snigdha Sajal Das","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have baby care?","answer":"Yes,it is baby care.","votes":"0","username":"Rajendra","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which model year?","answer":"2022","votes":"0","username":"Rajendra","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any installation cost?","answer":"Insallation is fully free of cost","votes":"0","username":"Saravanan…","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Any hidden cost during installation?","answer":"Insallation only free of cosy","votes":"0","username":"Saravanan…","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cost for installation? Like tap, powder etc.","answer":"Insallation free of cost","votes":"0","username":"Saravanan…","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do this machine has floor balance adjuster??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Saravanan…","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why promotional code deleted","answer":"sellers choice","votes":"0","username":"Romit sengupta","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the benefit of this product for prime membership","answer":"Speedy delivery and savings.","votes":"0","username":"Manish Pandey","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"This machine can load inverter connection","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Rajendra","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"I need Pay on delivery.","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"Rajendra","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which washing powder to be used in this machine's tub,to make it clean?","answer":"Dear Customer,You can use any Brand Detergent power or Liquid for Washing purpose meant for Top Load Washing Machine. Most of the brands mention if the product is suitable for Top Load Washing. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"This washing machine having dryer?","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. Spin Cycle is available which removes moisture from clothes after washing. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the exact warranty policy associated with this specific product? (Samsung India website says 120 months warranty, right?)","answer":"Dear Customer,You will get 2 years warranty on product and 2 years warranty on motor from Samsung India. Samsung India Official webpage showing same warranty details. For more details you can contact our support team on toll free number 1800-40-7267864 and whats app number 1800-5-7267864. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is that dry washing there,","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. Air Wash Feature is not available in this Washing Machine model. There is Spin Cycle available which removes moisture from clothes and make laundry dry. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much the warrnaty period for motor 2 or 10 years. And if 2 years how to extend it?","answer":"2 yrs","votes":"0","username":"Manish Pandey","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"One double bed quilt wash in this machine?","answer":"Yes if it's not too heavy","votes":"0","username":"S.arshar","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to drain water if I do not select Spin function ?","answer":"Dear Customer,The Rinse Cycle will automatically work to drain soapy water out. Also you can select Rinse cycle manually. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many Stars","answer":"3","votes":"0","username":"Manish Pandey","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this have a dryer ?","answer":"Yes it has dryer... it is a fully automatic washing machine...","votes":"0","username":"Ganesh Ramanathan","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Used this machine twice or thrice since my purchase a month ago and the machine wont switch on today so any idea on how to claim warranty","answer":"Call the call center","votes":"0","username":"Shoneit","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will I receive the new model ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Cp","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Automatic meaning wash rinse spin and even dry?","answer":"Correct","votes":"0","username":"vinod kumar sharma","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Samsung provide 10 year  warranty on motor but hear only 4 year why","answer":"Additional","votes":"0","username":"vinod kumar sharma","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is finial price to purchage the washing machine at 17/7/22","answer":"13500","votes":"0","username":"Guddu","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Tub is steel or plastic","answer":"Stanless steel daimond cut design","votes":"0","username":"Kadir","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does machine stop if the water pressure is low ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Kadir","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is energy saving rating?","answer":"Compared to the earlier machines, i am giving my opinion... 1. Against 2 hrs washing time for 5.5kg, it takes less than an hour to wash 6.5kg 2. It takes lesser water 3. Very clean wash 3. Very low noise even during final spin... and relatively at a shorter time... hope got the reply...lower running time and a good wash... subject to less than 17 days observation, as of now...see less","votes":"0","username":"S M.","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya spin cancellation ka provision h iss model m","answer":"This machine shows each stage of washing in normal mode. You may manually switch off at any stage. So you may stop in spin mode.  Power saver mode also may be used. This is my opinion  as per my understanding of the machine as explained to me by the person who came to install the machine from the company and l am not an expert or technically qualified person.see less","votes":"0","username":"S M.","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is energy saving rating?","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. This model is not applicable for energy star rating. However it comes with energy-saving cycle which helps save energy without compromising in wash quality. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it dry cloth also?","answer":"Dear Customer,This Washing Machine comes with Spin cycle to remove moisture from laundry. It also comes with Monsoon cycle to speed up drying process. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Tub is steel or plastic","answer":"Dear Customer,This Washing machine model drum is made of stainless steel. Diamond Drum’s unique “soft curl”design washes clothes very effectively, while treating them with care. Its smooth,diamond-shaped ridges are gentle on even delicate items. The small water exit holes also prevent fabric from becoming trapped and damaged. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does machine stop if the water pressure is low ?","answer":"Dear Customer,Low water pressure will work however it may take time to fill water for washing and start washing cycle. Desired water pressure requirement (Mpa (kg.f/cm2)) of this model is 0.05-0.78 (0.5-8.0) . Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"WHat is the energy saving rating for this model ?","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. This model is not applicable for energy star rating. However it comes with energy saving cycle which helps save energy without compromising in wash quality. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the manufacturing date of the said washing machine?","answer":"Dear Customer,This model was first available in 2020 however you will get latest stock depending upon availability. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is finial price to purchage the washing machine at 17/7/22","answer":"Dear Customer,To check price after discount please visit Amazon webpage of this model. You can also check additional offers like exchange or card offers. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"The washing machine has very loud noise  during washing .just bought yesterday .my lg machine was smooth .sny problem","answer":"Ask customer care","votes":"0","username":"Debu","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ed51cfba6a787843c7d"},"product_asin":"B0861BRS3B","QAs":[{"question":"Does the lid come down slowly or does it just drops down?","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. This Washing Machine model is not available with soft closing door. However it comes with Tempered Glass Window providing durability to door lid. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"My machine manufacturing year","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Gautam","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hard water can be use by this machine?","answer":"Yes, but more frequent service might be needed","votes":"0","username":"Sreenivasa Chandan","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Hitter available in this machine?","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. Automatic temperature control feature is not available. You can use hot water in this fully automatic washing machine however temperature should be equal to or below 50°C. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is any problem using bore water","answer":"Bore water contains Hard Water Which means it will take more water and the cleaning efficiency will be less !! But yes u can use !!","votes":"0","username":"Shri","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"During Power cut, is it have memory for again start automatically where it finish ? How to set or test. It is not work for me.","answer":"Yes automatic work start after power cut where we left","votes":"0","username":"SUDHANSHU SHEKHAR","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty on site hai kya","answer":"Dear Customer,Yes, Onsite warranty is available for this model from Samsung India. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"What are installation charges? Is purchase of accessories mandatory from installation engineer?","answer":"Dont buy it. Its a defective piece","votes":"0","username":"Ayesha Tabassum","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Dose it works with salt water?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Raio","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its a inventor washing machine?","answer":"Dear Customer,This model has inbuilt digital inverter technology which gives you greater energy efficiency, less noise and long-lasting performance. Digital inverter technology uses strong magnets for a quieter and more powerful performance, but consumes less energy. It provides outstanding durability, backed up by 12 years warranty on motor. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Drains by gravity via valve of with pump where drain pipe is kept at 100cm","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for  your query. A standpipe in height of 90-100 cm is recommended. The drain hose must be connected through the hose clip to the standpipe, and the standpipe must fully cover the drain hose. At the time of installation our service engineer will assist with best possible drainage setting during installation.Hope this is  of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Drain position","answer":"Backside","votes":"0","username":"Jatinder","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to book exchange of old washing machine to new samsung washing machine?","answer":"Already available on Amazon","votes":"0","username":"Digant J.","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it drying","answer":"Yes it does drying","votes":"0","username":"Madhukar Balachandra","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we adjust water level as per our requirement","answer":"It is automatic and it uses its own logic to adjust water level based on the cloths inside","votes":"0","username":"Madhukar Balachandra","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use hard water in this washing machine?","answer":"Dear Customer,You can use hard water for laundry washing. For best results, you can use a softener. Also periodically run Eco Tub Clean cycle. Eco Drum Clean technology keeps your front load washer fresh without using harsh chemicals. And it can even notify you automatically when it needs cleaning. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"If noone calls for installation..who shld we contact ????","answer":"Amazon customer care first and then try with Samsung customer care","votes":"0","username":"Madhukar Balachandra","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"this machine have in built heater","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Madhukar Balachandra","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any Warranty card ,I may have not received it.can I get some pictures","answer":"Yes available in box","votes":"0","username":"Digant J.","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hot water available?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Jatinder","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the machine has other colours","answer":"Couldn't find any other colors","votes":"0","username":"Jatinder","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Where we can add surf in it","answer":"there is a place written Detergent !! u can place it there","votes":"0","username":"Shri","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many liters of water required for 7kg machine 1 wash?","answer":"It takes water automatically","votes":"0","username":"Shri","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"After activation child lock can we deactivate or not and machine cycle working start when it was stopped or not ?","answer":"Dear Customer,You can activate or De-activate child lock without interfering the Washing Cycle which is running. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hot water wash available or not","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. In-Built Heater is not available in this Washing Machine model. However you can use hot water in this fully automatic washing machine having temperature range equal to or below 50°C. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can wash cycles timing be changed?","answer":"Dear Customer,Yes, You can change Water Level, Wash Time, Rinse Time and Spin Time Manually. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Suitable for hard water or salty water","answer":"Dear Customer,You can use hard water for washing however softner is advisable and using descaler meant for Washing machine. Also periodically run Eco Tub Clean cycle. Eco Drum Clean technology keeps your front load washer fresh without using harsh chemicals. And it can even notify you automatically when it needs cleaning. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it dry the clothe","answer":"Yes there is a spin dry programme.","votes":"0","username":"CHANDI CHARAN SINHA","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please tell me anyone which washing machine is best","answer":"That is a very generic question to answer. This Samsung fully automatic model is quite good. Very silent and couple of new features like monsoon drying etc.. Value for money","votes":"0","username":"T. R.","date":"2022-07-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Clothes remain wet after spin.. Not sure how to solve this issue..","answer":"They won't dry fully. You still have to put it out for drying. Ensure that nothing is blocking the water outlet pipe or that pipe is not clogged. And it is lower level than washing machine.","votes":"0","username":"T. R.","date":"2022-07-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I use bucket water instead of tap optionally I mean once in a while?","answer":"Yes you can","votes":"0","username":"deepak","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we delay installation at our conveninet time and date as I am not avialable at home for 3-4 days after delivery ?","answer":"Yes, installation can be scheduled. You will received a call from local service centre and they would ask uou about uohr preferred date and time to schedule the installation.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Product name","answer":"Samsung 7 Kg, 5 star fully automatic inverter washing machine with roller at bottom to keep your washed clothes tangle free.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to change the delivery date","answer":"Call customer care and reschedule","votes":"0","username":"deepak","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this 5 Star rating and does it have inverter built into it?","answer":"No inverter built into it its washing machine only","votes":"0","username":"deepak","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which year model is this? 2021 or 2022?","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"WTS Tamil","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many programs available in this washing machine","answer":"Dear Customer,This washing machine comes with 10 cycles i.e. Aqua Preserve, Delicates, Eco Tub Clean, Energy Saving, Jeans, Normal, Option List (Drain, Adjustable Wash, Rinse, Spin), Quick Wash, Rinse + Spin and Super Clean. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the minimum wash time?","answer":"You can do a quick wash of 15mins","votes":"0","username":"Rahul","date":"2022-08-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I Installation it self without avoiding warranty.","answer":"Dear Customer,Installation by Samsung authorized service engineer is recommended. You get a call from support team to book installation request as per your convenient date and time slot. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is human interface is button","answer":"Dear Customer,Yes, touch panel is available for controlling and selecting wash cycles as per requirement. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which year model is this? 2021 or 2022?","answer":"Dear Customer,This washing machine model is available from 2020 however you will get latest stock as per the availability. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Only drying is possible","answer":"Dear Customer,You can select Spin cycle/monsoon cycle manually to speed up the drying process. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I use bucket water instead of tap optionally I mean once in a while?","answer":"Dear Customer,In This Samsung fully automotic washing machine water is taken automatically depending upon laundry load however you can also select water level manually as per requirement. Pouring water through bucket is not advisable. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it dry the clothe","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. Dryer feature is not available in this Top load fully automatic washing machine. Spin cycle is available to remove moisture from laundry after washing. Also you can select monsoon cycle to speed up the drying process. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"If we order now,Will you deliver 2022 manufactured product?","answer":"Dear Customer,This model is available from 2020 however you will get the latest stock as per availability. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this 5 Star rating and does it have inverter built into it?","answer":"Dear Customer,Yes, This washing machine comes with 5 Star energy rating that comes with digital inverter technology motor which gives you greater energy efficiency, less noise and long-lasting performance. Digital inverter technology uses strong magnets for a quieter and more powerful performance but consumes less energy. It provides outstanding durability, backed up by 12 years warranty on motor. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can use this product with tap water as when required","answer":"Of course you can","votes":"0","username":"Raio","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ed71cfba6a787843c8b"},"product_asin":"B09T6NH99B","QAs":[{"question":"It have drier","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"shashank","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या इसमे कपडा सुखाया जा सकता है।","answer":"सुखाना तो नहीं कहेंगे परंतु","votes":"0","username":"MOHD IBRAHIM SHAMSI","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Motor winding copper or aluminium?","answer":"Pur copper","votes":"0","username":"Rahu","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Motor winding coppee or aluminium","answer":"Pure copper","votes":"0","username":"Rahu","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Wash and drain motor dono ki warranty hai 5 year ki","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Rahu","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it available for open box deleivery?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Rahu","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Power consumption","answer":"Very low","votes":"0","username":"Rahu","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Supply of plastic cover to avoid dust ingress","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Rahu","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this product is having outlet pipe to drain water?","answer":"Yes. It comes with one bundled.","votes":"0","username":"Vinoth Parashuram Iyer","date":"2022-08-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ed91cfba6a787843c98"},"product_asin":"B08QP41KBP","QAs":[{"question":"क्या इसमें ब्लैंकेटdho सकते हैं","answer":"Yes small","votes":"0","username":"Sudhanshu Kumar","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87edd1cfba6a787843cba"},"product_asin":"B083G1WGLF","QAs":[{"question":"Waranty kitni","answer":"It has 5 year warranty","votes":"0","username":"G. Jayant","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Iski motor aluminum ki hai ya copper ki","answer":"No sure, because it's completely covered with plastic","votes":"0","username":"abhishek surya","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there a water selector knob (to switch water from wash to drain) on this product","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Anjan Biswas","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the tub material? Stainless steel or plastic?","answer":"Plastic","votes":"0","username":"Vinsc","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is material of the outer body?","answer":"Plastic","votes":"0","username":"Vinsc","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty kitani hai","answer":"1 year","votes":"0","username":"Vinsc","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 5star or not","answer":"No 0 star","votes":"0","username":"Vinsc","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does impeller moves in both direction","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Asiya Mohammed Salim topiya","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this comes with Inbuilt heater","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Anjan Biswas","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use spin feature and drain same time","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Santanu Roychowdhury","date":"2022-07-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Isme dryer h kya","answer":"इसमे water extractor है, जो पानी निचोड़ के आधे से ज्यादा सूखा देता है, it does not hav hot air dryer like tumble dryer","votes":"0","username":"Manish choudhary","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87edf1cfba6a787843cd8"},"product_asin":"B08D7RWNWK","QAs":[{"question":"Buzzer available in washing machine","answer":"Yes buzzer is available","votes":"0","username":"Raghu","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ee51cfba6a787843cf6"},"product_asin":"B07WGD8QQT","QAs":[{"question":"Where we claim warranty or services??","answer":"Whirlpool would help with warranty n services","votes":"0","username":"Rahul","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we return this machine smoothly if there is any damages from vendor?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Rahul","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there technician comes or not for installation","answer":"Yes the technician will came from whirlpool side for installation and will guide you the process to use.","votes":"0","username":"satya prakash","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"My washing not move properly means work properly ...","answer":"Contact whirlpool","votes":"0","username":"Rahul","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"how many king size bedsheets can be washed at a time","answer":"3 to 4","votes":"0","username":"Divya Yadav","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it invade poland?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Divya Yadav","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it available inspection on door when deliver","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Divya Yadav","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"i like this washing machine and want to exchange it with the old one i have could you please suggest on how it can be done?","answer":"Choose your productTap on buy nowChoose the option to exchangeFill your detailsExchange price options will be shownChoose and place your ordersee less","votes":"0","username":"Divya Yadav","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"When changing pipe from washer to drier, does it get messy? Is there any chance outside detergent can come back into tub when changing pipe?","answer":"Changing pipe is smoothly process.","votes":"0","username":"Saurabh suman","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the size of machine, length and width","answer":"Length and width given in 'details' page.","votes":"0","username":"Saurabh suman","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ee61cfba6a787843d0a"},"product_asin":"B08337R52J","QAs":[{"question":"Is this 5 year warranty for both wash and spin motors?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Bilal Ahmad Khankashi","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Dryer capacity","answer":"I think 2 to 3 kg","votes":"0","username":"Virender Pal Singh","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it working properly","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Virender Pal Singh","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How get technical support.Yester day delivered mechine","answer":"Not needed. But if needed than cal customer care","votes":"0","username":"Virender Pal Singh","date":"2022-08-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ee71cfba6a787843d15"},"product_asin":"B08HZ8RBF7","QAs":[{"question":"It's taking water very slowly And washing completed is also very late? what can I do For taking water speedly And washing in Less time ??????","answer":"Water intake in this machine is very good..But you need overhead tank with full force water flow,Also need to check your machine intake valve, it also may block by dust due to non cleaness at frequent time.see less","votes":"0","username":"Vikram Jadav","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"In how many  and in which colours this machine is available?","answer":"3 colors, read the description of products","votes":"0","username":"Vikram Jadav","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87ee91cfba6a787843d1b"},"product_asin":"B07NSRNF79","QAs":[{"question":"Blanket can be wash in machine or not","answer":"Yes but check weight of blanket after sok in water is not more then its capacity.","votes":"0","username":"Vardan Joshi","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87efa1cfba6a787843dcd"},"product_asin":"B08R8DGDSK","QAs":[{"question":"Do you send someone for installation and guiding how to use after purchase?","answer":"Yes, whirlpool representative came and demonstrated on how to use washing machine","votes":"0","username":"Jvs","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 5 star energy consumption?","answer":"Yes. It is.","votes":"0","username":"SP","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want delivery on tomorrow","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"Kiran salunkhe","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many times to need water in this machine","answer":"1 time and it will take autometically.","votes":"0","username":"Abdul Muheet Talha","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Jaise every washing machine tub k inner wall per dust net hoti h wesi is machhine me kahan h?","answer":"1 time","votes":"0","username":"Abdul Muheet Talha","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i just use dryer instead of washing and then drying?","answer":"Yes you can use the dryer","votes":"0","username":"M P Subramanian","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Water fall technology.","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"Kiran salunkhe","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it have auto restart option","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Vijay kumar","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c9d05a1cfba6a787857d08"},"product_asin":"B07SVFX64L","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have inverter","answer":"Yes it works on inverter","votes":"0","username":"praneeth","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62cf14271cfba6a7878b4366"},"product_asin":"B084CMDS7B","QAs":[{"question":"Does it has touch button panel or push buttons??","answer":"all are push buttons... besy washing machine in market... very usefull","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is everyone facing issues with Shaking during spin cycle?","answer":"no... if u don't use trolly.. machine shake like hell... always use it with trolly... iron trolly for better stability","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 100% dry","answer":"No. But it does rinse out most of the water in dry mode.You still need to dry it in air for 2-3hrs or maybe 5-6hrs during rainy season.Though the benefit is that the dry mode benefits for even western coastal region levels (maybe a few hrs more there during rainy season).Caution: the spin is at high rpm though intermittent but still for local market stitched clothes, if not cross stitched then it may open/ un-stitch.see less","votes":"0","username":"Umesh Rao","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62d1b7101cfba6a78791f43c"},"product_asin":"B09R1R7NMR","QAs":[{"question":"Do this Machine have in build Heater","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Sougata Sarkar","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many clothes can be washed at a time?","answer":"It depends on how big cloths you wash.  Normally I wash 8-10 adult shirts ones.  But this machine is not so good as front load machine.  Better i recommend front load","votes":"0","username":"Tuya","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62dc43231cfba6a787ac73ff"},"product_asin":"B072FPNN8K","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have dryer","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"H R Dinesh Babu","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i buy this washing machine in exchange of old ifb machine?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ANKIT KUMAR","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it have wheels","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ANKIT KUMAR","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which year model is this","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"ANKIT KUMAR","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"In this machine filter is mandatory","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ANKIT KUMAR","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"does it have aqua store function","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ANKIT KUMAR","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62dd94911cfba6a787b0c1c4"},"product_asin":"B07H187SQW","QAs":[{"question":"Can we stack a serie 2 bosch dryer under it? Where can we get a stacking kit?","answer":"You can get it separately but you won't get with product.","votes":"0","username":"Menka Praveen Dubey","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62dd94a31cfba6a787b0c20d"},"product_asin":"B07NZBLJSK","QAs":[{"question":"Is it also work for dryer ?","answer":"Not working fully dryer","votes":"0","username":"Bhikshapathi Ch","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62dee60e1cfba6a787b50fdd"},"product_asin":"B08J3KFLBS","QAs":[{"question":"What series model wlj2026din is?","answer":"This is a Series 4 machine.","votes":"0","username":"sarvesh sawant","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it belt driven or direct driven ?","answer":"Bosch machines are generally Belt driven unless specified.","votes":"0","username":"sarvesh sawant","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"The product images say galvanzied steel but the specification details say its stainless steel. which one is correct?","answer":"It's Galvanized steel.","votes":"0","username":"sarvesh sawant","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do i need a stablizer too ??","answer":"If you have frequent power cutoff or too much variation in power supply then it's better to use a stabilizer.","votes":"0","username":"sarvesh sawant","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the wlj2026din 6.5 kg bosch washing machine have both tangle wash and anti wrinkle feature and function???","answer":"Anti tangle is available, anti wrinkle is not available.","votes":"0","username":"sarvesh sawant","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I set it's temperature manually?","answer":"Yes, depending on the selected program.","votes":"0","username":"sarvesh sawant","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Noise from drum while spinning time","answer":"This is not absolutely silent but not too noisy.","votes":"0","username":"sarvesh sawant","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62ec15341cfba6a787d5b52a"},"product_asin":"B09C693228","QAs":[{"question":"Is it rat free","answer":"Same is not mentioned anywhere 😒","votes":"0","username":"Rahul kumar","date":"2022-08-04 00:00:00"}]}
